### Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy describes how Titan Multi Crypto Wallet (TTN) applications collect, use and share information about you. This policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites, including [https://titanprojects.co](https://titanprojects.co/), (collectively, the “Site”) or otherwise interact with us as described below.

This policy does not apply to the Titan Multi Crypto Wallet open source client software or the Titan Multi Crypto Wallet distributed open source global payment network accessed through that software (collectively, “Titanprojects ”), which may be accessed via our Site. Titan Multi Crypto Wallet does not own or control . However, if you access Titan Multi Crypto Wallet from a hyperlink on our Site, we may collect the information identified in the “Information We Collect Automatically” section below in connection with your use of Titanprojects applications. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies, which will disable any information we would collect from cookies. We use the information collected on Titanprojects solely to analyze trends and evaluate user engagement of Titanprojects, when accessed from our Site. We will not collect any of the information that you provide directly to Titanprojects applications. Additionally, if you access Titanprojects applications by any other method, other than through a hyperlink available via our Site, then we will not collect any information in connection with your use of [https://titanprojects.co](https://titanprojects.co/)

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the homepages of our Site or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

#### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

We collect the information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an online account, post messages to our forums or wikis or otherwise communicate with us.

The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, username, password, location and any other information you choose to provide.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY

We automatically collect certain information about you when you access or use our Site or transact business with us, including Log Information. We collect information about your use of our Site, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Site.

Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We may use cookies, web beacons (also known as “tracking pixels”) and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you interact with our Site or emails, including information about your browsing behavior on our Site. We use this information to improve our Site and your experience, see which areas and features of our sites are popular, count visits, understand campaign effectiveness and determine whether an email has been opened and links within the email have been clicked.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM OTHER SOURCES

We may also obtain information about you from other sources and combine that with information we collect about you.

#### USE OF INFORMATION

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;

Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in order to operate and improve our Site;

Manage your online account(s) and send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;

Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and

Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using our Site or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

#### SHARING OF INFORMATION

We may share information about you as follows:

With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;

In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation;

If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of us or any third party;

In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and

With your consent or at your direction.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

#### ANALYTICS SERVICES PROVIDED BY OTHERS

We engage third parties to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of our Site, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity.

#### SECURITY

We take reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

#### COOKIES

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject cookies, but note that doing so does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies used in connection with our Site. If you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Site.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy [Contact Us.](https://titanprojects.co/#contact)

[FAQs](https://titanprojects.co/faqs) [Privacy Policy](https://titanprojects.co/privacy_policy) [Terms and conditions](https://titanprojects.co/terms_condition) [Terms of use](https://titanprojects.co/terms_of_use) [Fees](https://titanprojects.co/fees) [\[email protected\]](https://titanprojects.co/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Copyright © 2024 titanprojects.co
